evermotion.org 2013-11-04

# Privacy policy

Privacy policy

What personal data we collect

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person.

When you register an account, purchase or download a product or participate in an online survey, we may collect information, including your name, mailing address, email address, phone number and other information you may be asked to provide. We do not store on file your credit card details you provide when you make a purchase on Evermotion.com.

How we process your personal data

The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on the latest products, announcements and events. It’s helping us to improve our services and content. If you don’t want to receive any emails from us, you can opt out anytime by updating your account preferences.  
We also use your personal data to develop new products and services or for internal data analysis and research.

Use of non-personal data

We may also collect non-personal data which does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may use and/or disclose non-personal data for any purpose.

Cookies

We may use “cookies” to better understand our website visitor’s behavior or to remember personal information when you use our website to offer you better and more personal experience.  
We treat all data collected by “cookies” as personal for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

Protection

Evermotion online services use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal data is collected. 

Disclosure to third parties

We shall not reveal any personal data and shall not provide or transfer the collected personal data to third parties – state or municipal authorities, companies, natural persons and others, except in the following cases:   
you have expressed your explicit consent during or after the registration process;   
the personal data is duly requested by competent authorities in compliance with the applicable law; or   
in other provided for by the applicable law.
